[{"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Is that what they call her -- female president?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's what happened to me, too.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "I'm devastated.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Were you disappointed as I was?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Absolutely, yes.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "ORGAN: Is that how you felt?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Hmm, well, let's see.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "What'd you rob?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "I mean, in Hollywood, people come back to life, don't they?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Well -- first of all, who cracked it up to be -- well, anyway.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Was it all that it's cracked up to be, being in bed with a naked Brad Pitt?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Well, from the reaction that women had to \"Thelma & Louise,\" it was an incredible lesson in the power of media images.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Why do you feel so exercised about this?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well -- so, I have an institute that's now -- a research- based institute.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "What kind of thing?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "The first female president.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Is that what you mean?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, in this race.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "It's more likely to be one of these tea party candidates because they're the only ones who are currently showing their faces in this particular race?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "You know...", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "It does, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "You know, I liked it very much.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Is it giving you a little bit of the taste?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I'm not sure that's everyone's reaction.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "That's an advantage, isn't it?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Well, in exactly what I was talking about in reference to kids' movies is have more female characters and have them do more interesting things.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Where could Hollywood still improve, do you think?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "We're in this together, right?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "You're not going to say no, are you?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "You're available?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "I'm ready.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "You can start Monday?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "That is true.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I'm a real mix.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Are you a good girl in real life?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "We had a late night.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "I heard after the Emmy triumph on Sunday, you had a rather late night, Julianna?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "That's a very good question And they do ask that often and I think it's different for every person.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "So, what does it mean to be a good wife?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Did you actually strike the poor man?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "I really think it would depend on the situation.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Would you stand by your man?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Well, actually, when I was -- when we're very little, my parents split when I was 1 and it was a very amicable split for the most part.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What were the memories you had of them splitting up in your life, that you came to the United States with your mother, and how much do you see of your father?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "In East Greenstone (ph), darling.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Where did you go?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "You didn't?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "No, I left when I was 13.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "You didn't go to the nightclub at East Greenstone, did you?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well, I think people are going to find out soon enough Sunday night on CBS.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "What -- what does that mean exactly?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "No, David Letterman was obsessed with asking what we would see in the first episode and he kept saying, \"Your butt, are we going to see your butt?\"", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Allegations?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "No butt at all?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "You're a Baltimore Ravens fanatic, right?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "...I did...", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Did you see (INAUDIBLE) last night?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I -- I enjoyed it as well.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "I mean, he took everybody down with it, didn't he?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Oh my goodness, I think there's even worse dangers than that.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Isn't there a drunk Tweeting danger?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "...would be definitely top of the list, I think, don't you?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Actually, no.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "I mean, are you as pathetically unlucky in love in real life as you are on screen?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "A beautiful girlfriend.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "What's wrong with him, I know.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "It's like, what's wrong with this guy?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Things are much better for me than Will Gardner, as far as his emotional life, yes.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "But in real life, things are a lot happier?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I, you know, my girlfriend Sophie is not only comfortable with it, she wants to see it.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "And is he comfortable with these steamy love scenes that they're about to unfurl on the nation?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "No, I've -- I said to him, I said, I think the first episode, honey, might be steamier than I thought and he said, \"Good, I'll send Sophie flowers.\"", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "And your husband, you've banned from watching?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Alicia.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "I'm what?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Well, as a man...", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Why is monogamy not feasible?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I don't think it ...you know, our show is based on -- on a lack of monogamy.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Arsenal -- Arsenal is playing on Saturday, you said, right?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Like betraying them as -- as -- in friendship or betraying their trust and if we -- if we -- we are so conditioned...", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Do you, like what?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Yes, but -- but if you were to think about it this way that, you know, (a) it's a physical thing, it's a desire that we have and we can't, you know, we can -- if you are kind with it then maybe it's going to be OK.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Isn't cheating on them betraying their trust?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "I think a big -- big factor is when you have children and you're raising a family, staying together.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "Christine?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "It feels good because it makes your children happy.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "Do you understand (INAUDIBLE) character?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "ARANSKI: Yes, in fact, you asked Julianna about the women who stand by their men instead of deserting them and I think a big factor, for instance, Silda, she had two daughters, two daughters of an age to really know what was going on.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Do you understand why her character, then, would stand by her man?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Do you think he's inherently an evil person?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Yes, but he's still got -- he's still got chink in his armor.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Wouldn't he, in the end, do anything for political gain?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Yes, it's just kind of slanted a little further.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Does he have a moral compass, though?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "And -- and you get to see a whole different side of him which is really exciting.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "In real life.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Do you (INAUDIBLE), you have got an ex- wife?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "I have a husband.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Yes, and in real life you've also recently gone through a civil partnership?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "I don't know, whatever you think I should know.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "What would you like to know, Piers?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "OMFG.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "Yes, after -- after you lost, right?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Are you sure now that you're on the right side of the fence?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "You actually went and saw Magnus at his home, didn't you?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "A remarkable man and a beautiful soul.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "But he's a remarkable man, isn't he?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "I don't even know what you're talking about.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "How about those Bills?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Well, they have to come out of the hotel room, right?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "There's a lot of suspicion.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "When do you realize they're at it?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "She's got a new hairdo.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "So, are you confirming, unequivocally, that sex took place?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "He's not going to waste that kind of money is my sense, not his character.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "ARANSKI: Yes, I mean, I think any adult who goes to a hotel where it's $7,800 for the night, I mean, you're not going to sit there for $7,800 and just hold hands?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110924pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Have you all seen the first episode?", "qSentId": 733}]